# Jakub Łukasz **Młokosiewicz**

jmlokosiewicz@gmail.com | Personal projects: <a href="https://hckr.pl">https://hckr.pl</a>



# Introduction

During my career, I used mostly JavaScript (TypeScript), C++, Python, and PHP (with MySQL). I also had some experience with Kotlin, Java, and C#. I think I don't have trouble changing tools like languages, frameworks, and I always try to adapt to specific project demands to get things done the best way possible. I'm keen on asking questions and inspiring thoughtful dialog.

# Work experience

February 2021 - now

Red Sky (Backend Developer)

Technologies: Python, AWS, pySpark, MongoDB, terraform

development and refactoring of data science / big data pipelines

May 2020 - January 2021

Skinwallet (Full Stack Developer)

Technologies: TypeScript, Elm, Node.js, MySQL, RESTful API

- development of both front- and backend of a market platform for exchanging skins from games in a functional fashion based on provided designs and bussiness needs: <a href="https://skinwallet.com/market">https://skinwallet.com/market</a>
- integration with Google Merchant Center

September 2018 - April 2020

### Siili Solutions (Software Engineer)

- modern car cockpit display: issues analysis and fixing (Kanzi Studio, C++, internal tools)
- Qt GUI analytics library: <a href="https://auto.siili.com/our-work-hmi-analytics">https://auto.siili.com/our-work-hmi-analytics</a>
   (C++, Qt, QML)
- front-end for application optimizing plow routes with access roles and localization (TypeScript, React, Redux, rxjs, styled-components)
- Alexa skill informing about the car status: demo with per user configurations (via account linking) modifiable by a mobile friendly web app (TypeScript, ask-sdk, AWS Lambda, Firebase [Auth, DB], React)
- front-end for internal staffing tool: bugfixing and implementing new features (TypeScript, React, Redux, rxjs, styled-components)
- progressive web app for tracking of smart pallets with map, CRUD, search (TypeScript, React, Redux, rxjs, styled-components, Mapbox, AWS Amplify)

**July 2015 – September 2016** 

**brightONE Poland** (Junior Software Engineer)

Technologies: C++, Python, internal tools

- analysis of problem reports concerning a voice command subsystem in car's infotainment
- voice dialog modelling

#### July 2014 - September 2014

#### Red Sky (Intern)

Technologies: Python, JavaScript, MVC, SQL, ORM, HTML, CSS

- implementation of a comment system in *Domain Driven Design* methodology
- implementation of a view of recent activities of user's friends in a social website –
   added posts, comments and likes

#### 2010 - 2013

### **Staniszewski-IT** (part-time)

Technologies: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Joomla, HTML, CSS

- implementation of a tool for regular reporting of positions of customers' websites in the Google search results for given keywords
- implementation of the tool facilitating issuing invoices in *active.invoice* system, based on data from company's online shops
- modifications of Virtuemart software, coding website templates for Joomla CMS

# Education

#### 2019 - now

### West Pomeranian University of Technology, Szczecin

Master's studies in the field of *Computer Science and Information Technology* Specialization *Human-oriented computer systems* 

#### 2012 - 2016

### West Pomeranian University of Technology, Szczecin

Engineering studies in the field of Computer Science and Information Technology

# Other

English B2/C1

OS Linux, Mac OS, Windows

MS Office good knowledge
Driving licence category B

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (Data Protection Directive)